Alderfer, S. Stanley Arbitration Files 5576
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Arbitration Decisions, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 23: Perry Equipment Corporation and Perry Products Company vs. United Independent Union, Local 1, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    10/10/72. Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay.
  - Item 24: ICI America, Incorporated, Atlas Point Plant vs. International Union of Allied and Technical Workers, District 50, Local 12886, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    10/31/72. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 25: American Chain and Cable Company, Incorporated, New York Chain Plant vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1852, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    10/10/72. Issue: Overtime--Suspension; Improper Assignment, Remedy.
  - Item 26: RCA Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 103, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    5/3/72. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
  - Item 27: Chemical Leaman Tank Lines, Incorporated vs. Tank Truck Workers Union, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    9/26/72. Issue: Layoff.
  - Item 28: Pennsylvania Steel Foundry and Machine Company, Hamburg, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6541, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    9/26/72. Issue: Schedules of Work.
  - Item 29: The Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania vs. Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    9/28/72. Issue: Suspension.
  - Item 30: Scott Paper Company, Chester, Pennsylvania vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 448, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    9/22/72. Issue: Overtime.
  - Item 31: International Mill Service, Division of I.U. Industrials, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6303, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 31)
    11/8/72. Issue: Discharge.
- Arbitration Decisions, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Penn Fruit Company, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 929, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    1/10/73. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 2: Precision Steel Division of Predco, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6177, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    7/10/73. Issue: Seniority.
  - Item 3: Fair-Tex Mills, Incorporated vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local 1665, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    6/30/73. Issue: Suspension.
  - Item 4: National Casein of New Jersey vs. Independent Union, Local 707, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    6/19/73. Issue: Discharge; Suspension.
  - Item 5: Standard Steel, a Division of Titanium Metals Corporation of America vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1940, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    5/29/73. Issue: Assignment of Jobs; Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems.
  - Item 6: Bishop Tube Company/Whittaker Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7566, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    5/31/73. Issue: Suspensions--Discharge vs. Suspension; Plant Rules--Safety Rules.
  - Item 7: Ward Chocolate Company, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District Lodge No. 1, Local 775, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    6/11/73. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 8: Textile Machinery Divisions, Rockwell International, Reading, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6996, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    5/7/73. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 9: Food Fair Stores, Incorporated vs. Retail Clerks International Association, Local 1357, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    5/21/73. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 10: New Jersey Water Company vs. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, Local 473, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    4/23/73. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 11: Star Dental Manufacturing Company, Incorporated vs. International Union of Radio, Electrical and Machine Workers, Local 123, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    3/20/73. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 12: Abington School District, Board of School Directors vs. Abington School Service Personnel Association, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    3/20/73. Issue: Classification of Jobs--Rates of Pay.
  - Item 13: Frank M. Weaver and Company, Incorporated, Lansdale, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3187, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    2/5/73. Issue: Classification of Jobs; Discharge.
  - Item 14: Boiler Engineering and Supply Company, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7004, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    7/10/73. Issue: Bumping.
  - Item 15: Metropolitan Hospital, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania vs. National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees, Division of Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union, Local 1199C, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    1/25/73. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 16: Food Fair Stores, Incorporated vs. Retail Clerks and Store Employees Union, Local 1371, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    10/9/73. Issue: Promotions.
  - Item 17: Metropolitan Edison Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 603, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    2/13/73. Issue: Suspension; Discipline.
  - Item 18: Southern New Jersey Newpapers, Incorporated vs. International Typographical Union, Camden Typographical Union No. 132, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    9/15/73. Issue: Jurisdiction; Management Rights.
  - Item 19: The Boeing Company, Vertol Division vs. United Automobile Workers, Local 1069, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    3/29/73. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 20: Atlas Powder Company, Reynolds Plant, Tamaqua, Pennsylvania vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-868, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    11/30/73. Issue: Seniority.
  - Item 21: General Battery Corporation, Reading, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5227, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    11/28/73. Issue: Reinstatement.
  - Item 22: Penco Products, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6737, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    11/13/73. Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay.
  - Item 23: General Machine Corporation, Emmaus, Pennsylvania vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 1890, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    10/15/73. Issue: Union Security.
  - Item 24: The York Water Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 151, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    9/29/73. Issue: Schedules of Work--Holiday and Time Off Schedules.
  - Item 25: Food Fair Stores, Incorporated vs. Retail Clerks International Association, Local 1357, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    7/30/73. Issue: Reinstatement.
  - Item 26: Allentown, Pennsylvania, City of vs. Service Employees International Union, Local 395, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    9/15/73. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
  - Item 27: J.W. Rex Company, Lansdale, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5621, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    9/29/73. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
  - Item 28: Broad Street Hospital and Medical Center, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania vs. National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees, Division of Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees Union, Local 1199C, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    8/31/73. Issue: Union Security.
  - Item 29: J. Bass and Company vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local 1669, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    7/31/73. Issue: Reinstatement.
  - Item 30: Downington Plastics Machinery Division, Beloit, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7424, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    7/30/73. Issue: Discipline.
  - Item 31: Warner Company, Cedar Hollow Plant vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    7/25/73. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 32: Krylon Department, Division of Borden Chemical, Borden Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5740, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    7/30/73. Issue: Vacation Pay.
  - Item 33: Strick Corporation vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1354, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    7/18/73. Issue: Discharge.
  - Item 34: Plymouth Tube Company, Horsham, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6342, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 32)
    9/20/73. Issue: Suspension; Discharge.
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, #72-2195 - Michelina Linardi vs. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 2532, District Council 90, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
  12/14/77. Issue: Reinstatement.
- Dorr-Oliver Incorporated, Hazleton, Pennsylvania vs. Office and Professional Employees International Union, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
  9/19/77. Issue: Contract Interpretation.
- Asplundh Tree Expert Company vs. Local 126, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
  7/15/77. Issue: Rates of Pay.
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, Department of Transportation, #77-18 - Stewart Chadrow vs. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 2607, District Council 88, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
  8/19/77. Issue: Discharge.
- Leeds and Northrup Company vs. United Automobile Workers, Local 1350, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
  6/23/77. Hearing Cancelled.
- P.S. Stauffer and Sons, Willow Grove, Pennsylvania vs. International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 542, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 6)
  9/3/77. Issue: Discrimination.
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, Department of Public Welfare, Harrisburg State Hospital vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, District Council 90, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 7)
  7/13/77. Issue: Suspension.
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of vs. American Federation of State County and Municipal Employees, Local 1952, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 8)
  7/1/77. Issue: Suspension.
- Hooker Chemicals and Plastics Corporation, Ruco Division vs. United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, Local 482, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
  9/27/77. Issue: Vacations.
- American Metal Works, Incorporated, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4659, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
  6/4/77. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
- Permutit Company, Incorporated, a subsidiary of Sybron Corporation, Lancaster, Pennsylvania vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1918, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
  5/27/77. Issue: Discharge.
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of vs. Conference of State Police, Fraternal Order of Police, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 12)
  6/1/77. Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay.
- Trane Thermal Company, Conshohocken, Pennsylvania vs. United Automobile Workers, Local 416, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 13)
  5/26/77. Issue: Contract Interpretation.
- American Metal Works, Incorporated, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4659, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 14)
  6/7/77. Issue: Assignment of New Jobs.
- Pennsylvania Electric Company vs. System Council U-12, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
  7/1/77. Issue: Discharge.
- Hale Fire Pump Company, Conshohocken, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7924, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
  6/14/77. Issue: Suspension.
- AMETEK, Schutte and Koerting Division, Cornwell Heights, Pennsylvania vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 929, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
  6/30/77. Issue: Discharge.
- Temple University vs. District 1199C, The Guild of Professional, Technical and Clerical Employees, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 18)
  6/2/77. Issue: Leaves of Absence.
- Heintz Division, Kelsey-Hayes Company, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania vs. United Automobile Workers, Local 834, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
  5/24/77. Issue: Discharge.
- Asplundh Manufacturing Division, Chalfont, Pennsylvania vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 772, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 20)
  5/19/77. Issue: Discharge.
- General Metalcraft, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 326, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 21)
  5/17/77. Issue: Discharge; Discipline.
- Aluminum Shapes, Incorporated vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 837, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 22)
  5/10/77. Issue: Insubordination; Discharge.
- Leeds and Northrup Company vs. United Automobile Workers, Local 1350, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 23)
  5/3/77. Issue: Discharge.
- Louderback Transportation Company, Incorporated, vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 513, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 24)
  4/2/77. Issue: Discharge.
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, Bureau of Collection vs. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, District Council 88, Local 2497, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 25)
  5/2/77. Issue: Suspension.
- Hub Tool Manufacturing and Machine Company, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7841, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 26)
  4/30/77. Issue: Vacations.
- Teledyne AMCO, Mohnton, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1333, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 27)
  4/22/77. Issue: Assignment of Jobs; Bumping; Standards of Production.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 28)
  3/30/77. Issue: Theft--Company Property.
- Confer Smith and Company, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1972, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 29)
  3/21/77. Issue: Assignment of Jobs; Rates of Pay.
- Phoenix Forging Company, Division, Union Tank Car Company, Catasauqua, Pennsylvania vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Local 1506, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 30)
  5/14/77. Issue: Discipline--Discharge; Suspension.
- Sorensen Industries vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5424, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 31)
  3/10/77. Issue: Seniority; Recall.
- Wilmington, Delaware, City of vs. International Association of Firefighters, Wilmington Firefighters Local 1590, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 32)
  4/27/77. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
- The Heil Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6880, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 33)
  3/8/77. Issue: Suspension.
- NEAPCO, a division of Berwind Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2479, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 34)
  2/26/77. Issue: Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems.
- Pennsylvania Steel Foundry and Machine Company, Hamburg, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6541, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 35)
  2/15/77. Issue: Bumping; Schedules of Work.
- Shawnee-Penn Manufacturing Company, Incorporated, Bethlehem, Pennsylvania vs. United Furniture Workers of America, Local 90, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 36)
  2/24/77. Issue: Discharge.
- Reading Metals Refining Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 37)
  2/4/77. Cancelled.
- General Machine Corporation, Emmaus, Pennsylvania vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 1890, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 38)
  2/10/77. Issue: Overtime.
- Sun Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Lodge 802, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 39)
  2/3/77. Issue: Discipline.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 40)
  1/12/77. Issue: Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems.
- Allentown, City of, Lehigh County, Pennsylvania vs. Service Employees International Union, Local 395, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 41)
  1/6/77. Issue: Assignment of New Jobs; Rates of Pay.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 42)
  12/15/76. Issue: Fringe Benefits; Layoff.
- Allentown, Pennsylvania, City of vs. International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 302, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 43)
  12/10/76. Issue: Overtime.
- Cleland Simpson Company, a subsidiary of John Wanamaker, of Scranton, Pennsylvania vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 229, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 44)
  12/4/76. Issue: Holidays and Holiday Pay; Overtime.
- Hotpack Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Local 300, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 45)
  12/10/76. Issue: Recall; Seniority.
- Asplundh Tree Expert Company vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 772, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 46)
  12/3/76. Issue: Suspension.
- Sun Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Local 802, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 47)
  11/19/76. Cancelled.
- Continental Can Company, Plant No. 86, Reading, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5659, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 48)
  1/7/77. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Past Practice.
- Hofmann Industries, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5655, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 49)
  11/30/76. Issue: Suspension; Discharge.
- Disston, Incorporated vs. United Saw, File and Steel Products Workers of America, No. 22254, Federal Labor Union, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 50)
  11/26/76. Issue; Removal of Work From Bargaining Unit.
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, Department of Revenue vs. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 51)
  11/22/76. Issue: Discharge.
- Frank M. Weaver and Company, Incorporated, Lansdale, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3187, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 52)
  11/23/76. Issue: Cost of Living Increases.
- General Battery Corporation, Reading, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5227, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 53)
  11/6/76. Issue: Classification of Jobs; Rates of Pay.
- Sun Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company vs. Marine Draftsmen of the International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Local 804, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 54)
  11/9/76. Issue: Discharge.
- Atlas Powder Company vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-868, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 55)
  10/27/76. Issue: Discipline.
- Cellu Products Company vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Eagle Run Local 1338, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 56)
  11/4/76. Issue: Vacations.
- Delvar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 57)
  10/21/76. Issue: Equipment and Physical Facilities.
- General Battery Corporation, Reading, Pennsylvania vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 5227, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 58)
  10/21/76. Issue: Suspension; Assignment of Jobs.
- Lancaster, Pennsylvania, City of vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 59)
  10/28/76. Issue: Discharge.
- Asplundh Tree Expert Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 772, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 60)
  10/15/76. Issue: Discharge; Discrimination.
- Metropolitan Edison Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 803, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 61)
  10/1/76. Issue: Assignment of Jobs.
- Morysville Body Works, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6622, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 62)
  9/23/76. Issue: Seniority; Recall; Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems.
- Sun Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Lodge 802, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 63)
  9/17/76. Issue: Discipline; Discharge. (includes: bills, correspondence, and notes)
- Pepsi-Cola Bottling Company of Wilmington vs. Pepsi-Cola Employees Association, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 64)
  9/16/76. Issue: Discharge.
- Vertol Division, the Boeing Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1069, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 65)
  7/22/76. Issue: Recall.
- Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of, Bureau of Labor Relations vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, District Council 13, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 66)
  7/16/76. No Award, grievance withdrawn during hearing.
- Sun Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Lodge 802, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 67)
  7/16/76. Cancelled. (includes late cancellation bill)
- Stauffer Chemical Company, Delaware City PVC Plant vs. United Paperworkers International Union, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 68)
  7/10/76. Issue: Discipline.
- Temple University vs. the Guild of Professional, Technical and Clerical Employees, District 1199C, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 69)
  6/28/76. Issue: Classification of Jobs.
- SKF Industries, Incorporated, Hanover, Pennsylvania Plant vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 7343, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 70)
  6/17/76. Issue: Assignment of Jobs; Seniority.
- ITT Electron Tube Division vs. United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 644, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 71)
  6/10/76. Issue: Transfers.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 72)
  6/10/76. Issue: Incentive Pay and Incentive Systems.
- Delbar Products, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 43, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 73)
  6/18/76. Issue: Contracting Out.
- General Machine Corporation, Emmaus, Pennsylvania vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 1890, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 74)
  6/12/76. Issue: Working Conditions.
- General Machine Corporation, Emmaus, Pennsylvania vs. International Association of Machinists, Local 1890, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 75)
  6/8/76. Issue: Layoff; Red Circle Rates.
- Cardwell Industries vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 635, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 76)
  6/3/76. Issue: Rates of Pay.
- Wilmington, Delaware, City of vs. International Association of Firefighters, Wilmington Firefighters, Local 1590, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 77)
  6/30/76. Issue: Classification of Jobs; Elimination of Jobs.
- International Paper Company vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 1318, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 78)
  6/3/76. Issue: Suspension.
- Peter J. Schweitzer Division, Kimberly-Clark Corporation vs. United Paperworkers International Union, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 79)
  5/27/76. Issue: Classification of Jobs.